Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III - Emergency Boards
  - Sub-Series C. Board of Inquiry - Republic Aviation.
    - Republic Aviation Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists (and Other Unions) and vs. Republic Lodge 1987, International Association of Machinists., 1962 (Box 133, Folder All)
      Contains Agreements and Reports of a Presidential Board of Inquiry. 8/3/62.